So when T.S. came on, I already knew this is about to be a turn-up.
But it was such a turn-up that we ended up having to do two parts.
And I just loved her candor.
I'm going to end up being the serious person in some of these conversations
because the guest is going to take it to the hilt.
And baby, that is what T.S. Madison is always going to do.
Were you always someone who, always an exuberant, like, big mouth, big voice person?
Yeah, I was.
I used to get a lot of whoopings because I said everything I felt.
You can't say that.
And I'm a person that always went back and checked myself.
Maybe I said too much.
Or maybe I said it the wrong way.
Right, right, right, right.
Like, it was the truth, but it didn't have to cut like that.
It didn't have to do that.
I didn't have to do that.
So y'all forgive me for that.
But I meant what I said.
There's that.
Because you're like that.
Yes.
That's why I love you because you're that way.
Like, you eat.
But I understand where you're eating from.
You get me.
I do.
That's why I love you too.
I love you.
I always have.
I love you too.
But you're like, this is what happens.
And to honor you too.
We love you.
I love you too.
We love you too.
You love you too.
I love you too.
You used to live.
You know you who theye you and you.
You made me?